## SANGRAM K. SUNDARAY

## SOFTWARE DEVELOPER (WEB APPS & DAPPS)

### **PROFILE**

7+ years of experience in Web Application Development using Python & Django and modern responsive frameworks. Now working on Ethereum Blockchain for decentralized apps development.

Had also worked in Digital Marketing, Google Search Console & Analytics.

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

#### Remote/Freelance (April 2018 - present)

- ConVoyage Systems: Developed and working presently on Consortium based Decentralized App for logistics using Solidity for Smart Contracts and Truffle
- Marvin AI: Developed Intuitive Reseller Management Systems using Python & Django
- Worked for Fortune 500 Client PwC via Neukelp LLP, IIT Bhubaneswar & KIIT TBI
- Developed prototype for Document Abstraction Tool Using Python, Django & Postgresql, NLTK
- Reporting & Repository Maintenance

## FULL STACK DEVELOPER (WER & DATA)

#### SITSINDIA (Jan 2015 - APRIL 2018)

- Web Apps Development in LAMP Stack, Python-Django Stack & WordPress
- Prototyping Small Web Apps for Sales Presentation
- Managing Development team to Meet Projects Deadlines
- Web Apps Optimization(Google & Zoho Analytics)

# WEB DEVELOPER [PHP & MYSQL]

#### LIT Solution (Jan 2014- Jan 2015)

- Developed Responsive Web Apps for 15 mid-size clients
- Indivual contribution to School Management software using PHP4
- Wordpress App Management
- Responsive Design and Websites Maintenance
- improving Websites and Web apps Performance using Google Webmaster Tools

## MANAGEMENT TRAINEE [SALES]

#### AurolN LLP (Aug 2013 - Jan 2014)

- Sales Operations(US & Europe Region)
- - Sales Follow Up and Business Communication

### **EDUCATION** -

B.E. IN ELECTRONICS & COMMUNICATION

Biju Pattnaik College of Engineering, Bhubaneswar (2009 - 2013)

XIITH SCIENCE (2008)

Kendriya Vidyalaya HPCL JRD, Assam

XTH (2006)

Kendriya Vidyalaya HPCL JRD, Assam

PREFFERED TECH - STACK

**Front-End**: Bootstrap, HTML5, CSS3 **Backend**: Python-Django, Postgresql

**Blockchain:** Solidity, Truffle

Cloud(Deployment & Implementation: AWS & GCP

## OTHER DETAILS \_\_\_\_\_

Address: 760/1134, Near Pal Heights, Jaydev Vihar,

Bhubaneswar, Odisha

**Phone**: 99-37-82-6218

**E-mail:** sangramz@hotmail.com **Website:** sangramz.github.io